arena.wix.com 2013-08-06

# Wix.com Privacy Policy | Wix Arena

##  Wix.Com Privacy Policy

Effective Date: September 13, 2011 

1. General Principles 

This Privacy Policy describes how Wixpress Ltd. (“Wix.com”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [www.wix.com](http://www.wix.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

We built Wix.com to enable you to create and share web based content with your friends and people around you. We understand you may not want everyone to have access to your hosted at Wix.com; that is why we give you control of your personal content. 

Wix.com helps you share content with your friends and people around you. You choose what content you make available to the general users of Wix.com

Wixpress Ltd. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at: [support@wix.com](mailto:support@wix.com) or 1-800-6000-WIX (1-800-600-0949).  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe here. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through the Wix.com website.

Wix.com is based on the accumulation of user provided and/or formed content and there is an increasing amount of content being made available for Wix.com users. Wix.com sees it as its goal to help its users have as much content as possible available for their use while retaining each users privacy.

2\.  Acceptance 

By using or accessing Wix.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy statement covers any and all actions on the [www.Wix.com](http://www.wix.com/) website (the "Website"). 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our privacy staff at [privacy@Wix.com](mailto:privacy@Wix.com). 

3. Collection and Providence of Information and Content

When you visit Wix.com you provide us with two types of information: limited personal information and content you knowingly choose to disclose and/or post on the Wix.com website 

When you register with Wix.com, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your email address.

When you enter Wix.com, we use third party utility-tracking partners to collect your browser type and IP address through log files. This information is gathered for all Wix.com visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our website. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID and password to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Wix.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

The use of cookies by our tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy statement.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.  

You post User Content (as defined in the Wix.com Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and content. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed (or even harmed) by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

4. Billing information 

Should you sign up for a Charged Cervices (as defined in the Terms of Use), we will require your billing information along with information such as your name, phone number and address in order to process the transaction and to collect the fees involved.

We do not store your billing information, and this information will be discarded after your transaction has been processed. Nevertheless, the required information for your billing will be stored by our payment gateway company which will store your billing information on their secure payment gateway for as long as necessary to carry out the terms of your subscription.

We may retain the last 4 digits of your credit card number, and credit card type, so that you may identify the card used in the future.

Should you cancel your subscription, your billing information will be removed by the payment gateway company. 

5\. Sharing Your Content with Third Parties

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.   

Wix.com provides, as a main service, the ability of sharing created content with others — friends and people in your networks. 

We may provide information and/or personal user content to service providers to help us provide the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to provide you with our community blog, to send out email updates about Wix.com, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services and to provide you with our live chat services. In connection with these business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information and/or content for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.    

We occasionally provide demonstrations of user created content that allow non-users a glimpse into the Wix.com world. Such content is provided in a form which protects your content from any unauthorized editing and/or changing. 

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Wix.com service or using the Wix.com name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

We may offer or provide services jointly with other companies on Wix.com such as when you purchase your domain name through our Website. In such case we shall provide clear disclosure of such third party's in the providence of such service on Wix.com, and in such case we shall be entitled to share customer information such as user ID with such third party in connection with your use of such joint services. In any case in which the ownership of Wix.com's business shall change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations.

When you use Wix.com, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos or other information, may be shared with other users. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk.

6. Communications from the Website

We will use your email address in order to send you promotional emails. If you no longer wish to receive these emails you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the promotional communications which you receive.

7. Links

Wix.com may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Wix.com or posted on the Wix.com website.

8. Public Forums

Our Website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at: [privacy@Wix.com](mailto:privacy@Wix.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

9. Changing or Removing Content

Access and control over personal content on Wix.com is possible through the content editing tools. Wix.com users may modify or delete any of their personal content at any time by logging into their account. Any such changes will be updated immediately. Users who wish to deactivate their Wix.com account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to users of Wix.com.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at [support@wix.com](mailto:support@wix.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

10\.  Security 

Wix.com takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information and content. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards which protect your account information and uploaded content. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, these transactions are processed over an industry standard SSL/TLS connection, with a minimum of 1024-bit encryption. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information or data to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions regarding the security of Wix.com Website, please contact us at [privacy@Wix.com.com](mailto:privacy@Wix.com.com).

11. Wix pro directory

If you are selected to be a part of our Wix pro directory, we will list you in our publicly accessible member directory. If you no longer wish be listed in our directory, you may contact us at [support@wix.com](mailto:support@wix.com).

12\.  Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information.  We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request the removal of your testimonial you may contact us at [support@wix.com](mailto:support@wix.com).

13\.  Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or on our Website. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).  

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic and to provide notices to participants.

Wix may use third party service providers to conduct surveys or contests. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

14. Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions  

Your use of Wix.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our General Terms of Use and all of its general provisions including warranty disclaimer, limitation of liability, indemnity and choice of law. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and to any of your account.

15. Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@Wix.com.com](mailto:privacy@Wix.com.com). You may also contact us by mail at: 40 Nemal Tel Aviv St. Tel Aviv, Israel.
